http://www.truefoodsmarket.com/pages/privacy

Contact Us
PROMOTION SALE - UP TO 50%!
True Foods Market - Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Your information, whether public or private, will NOT be sold,
exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason
whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of
delivering the purchased product or service requested.
What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emails (only if you signed up for our Newsletter)
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used
to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 1/09/2013
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Almonds Raw Organic - 2 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Oat Bran Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a True Organics Bee Sure Super Food Drink Mix - 16 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Napa Valley Sesame Oil Cold Pressed Organic - 12.7 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Vital Wheat Gluten Flour - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bragg's Sprinkle Herbs & Spices Seasoning - 1.5 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Let's Do...Organic Edward & Sons Shredded Coconut Organic - 8 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Vita Spelt Vita Spelt Lasagna Organic - 8 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Traditional Medicinals Throat Coat Herbal Syrup - 4 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Simply Organic Classic Caesar Dressing Mix Organic - 3 x 1.25 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Almonds Raw Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a American Health More Than A Multiple For Women - 90 tablets
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Coconut Shredded Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Lundberg Wild Rice Blend, Eco-Farmed - 25 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Wilderness Family Naturals Mayo (soy free) Organic - 16 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bragg's Vinaigrette Salad Dressing Organic - 12 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a American Health More Than A Multiple For Men - 90 tablets
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Stevita Stevia Dent Peppermint - 12 pcs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Sunflower Seeds Raw Domestic Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bragg's Ginger & Sesame Salad Dressing - 12 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Buttermilk Biscuit Mix - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Rapunzel Chocolate Hazelnut Butter Organic - 8.8 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Lundberg Jasmine Brown Rice Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Andean Naturals Quinoa Elbows Organic - 5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Lundberg White Arborio Rice Eco-Farmed Gluten-Free - 2 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bakery on Main Apple Cinnamon Walnut Granola - 12 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Knudsen Just Black Currant - 32 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a NuNaturals Throat Control Spray - 2 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a SEA-90 Water Soluble Sea Solids - 50 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Coconut Shredded Organic - 2.5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Body Rescue Alkalizing Tea Apple Cinnamon (20 bags) - 1 box
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Simply Organic Hollandaise Sauce Mix Organic - 12 x 1 oz.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Eden Foods Lentils with Onion & Bay Leaf Organic - 15 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Bulk Agave Blue Light Organic - 32 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Body Rescue Alkaline Booster pH Protector Drops - 1.25 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Pacific Foods Chicken Broth Low Sodium Organic - 32 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Oregon's Wild Harvest Turmeric - 60 veg caps
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Eden Foods Sauerkraut in glass Fine Cut Organic - 32 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Barbara's Bakery Snackimals Snickerdoodle - 7.5 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Barbara's Bakery Snackimals Chocolate Chip - 7.5 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Amy's Fire Roasted SW Veg Soup Organic - 14.3 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Gardentime Orzo Whole Wheat Organic - 2.5 lbs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Garden of Eatin' White Corn Tortilla Chips Fiesta Size - 22 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Traditional Medicinals Throat Coat for Kids Organic - 1 box
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Traditional Medicinals Herba Tussin Cough Syrup - 4 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Oregon's Wild Harvest Slippery Elm 400 mg Organic - 90 veg caps
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Napa Valley Sesame Oil Cold Pressed - Organic - 1 gallon
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Maine Coast Sea Salt with Sea Veg - 1.5 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a American Biotech Labs Silver Biotics - 16 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
Someone Awesome Purchased a Wilderness Family Naturals Chocolate Syrup Organic - 20 ozs.
hr
mins ago.
^
